Everyone is a suspect.
Invitation to a Murder is a mystery, thriller, tv
movie film directed by Stephen Shimek.
A reclusive billionaire invites six seemingly random strangers
to his island estate in the south of England.
Aspiring detective Miranda Green finds the mysterious
invitation too alluring to pass up.
When another guest turns up dead, Miranda must get to the
bottom of the malicious plot behind the gathering.
Miranda Green, played by Mischa Barton.
Donald Walker, played by Chris Browning.
Carmen Blanco, played by Bianca A. Santos.
Phillip Armstrong, played by Giles Matthey.
Lu Wang, played by Grace Lynn Kung.
Lawrence Kane, played by Seamus Dever.
Invitation to a Murder (released as An Invitation to Murder in the UK) is a 2023 American murder mystery
film directed by Stephen Shimek and starring Mischa Barton, Chris Browning, Bianca A.
Santos, and Giles  Matthey.
It was released by Lionsgate on April 25, 2023.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.